Bueno.
Okay.
Stop, stop, stop.
What are you doing?
No.
Tip number one:
close your eyes.
Close your eyes, please.
Gino, you too.
Imagine something delightful.
Me, for example.
I'm just kidding.
Imagine
you're
seven years old.
There are no problems,
no bad things,
only happiness and bright future.
Your mom just has left freshly
baked pie in the kitchen.
It smells like...
like vanilla,
and your lips is naturally
naturally trying to eat.
Come on, prince.
Stop.
Don't open your eyes and
keep listening to me, please.
Take small breath.
Sense each other smell.
Nice.
Reach out your lips.
Let the desire build
and taste this cream.
Get away from me!
What the hell?
Too bad.
You're just my type.
So you and Gina just
just... just friends?
Welcome to acting.